Guide to the Theodore H. Geballe Papers SC0357
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2010-055
  - Correspondence M-O 1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence P-R 1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence S 1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence T-Z 1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence A-C 1973 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence D-G 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence H-K 1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence L-N 1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence O-R 1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence S-U 1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence V-Z 1973 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence A-D 1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence E-G 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence H-K 1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence L-N 1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence O-R 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence S-T 1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence U-Z 1974 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence A-C 1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence D-G 1975 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence H-K 1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence L-N 1975 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence O-S 1975 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence T-Z 1975 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Bound volume of papers and articles by various authors on Germanium and Silicon, 1954-61 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1967 Applied Superconductivity Conference Abstracts (includes annotations by Geballe) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Reprints and paper by Geballe, 1963-67 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Bound portfolio: High resolution electron micrographs of 2H-NbS2 and 2H-NbSe2 recorded with the cryo-electron microscope…. H. Fernandez-Moran, M. Ohtsuki, C. Hough. The Electron Microscope Laboratory, University of Chicago, May/June 1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Other electron microscopy images (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Color slides of Vac Station, Sept. 14, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2015-101
  - Malcolm "Mac" Beasley letter to Theodore H. Geballe, 1972 Nov 9 (Box 1)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2017-004
  - Howland, R., undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Hull, G.W., undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Little, William A., undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Kittel, C., undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Kittel, Peter, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Kompfner, R., undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Laughlin, R.B., undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Talvacchio, J., undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Tauc, J., undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Thompson, A.H., undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Student: Mael, David Jeffrey, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Marezio, M., undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Matthias, B., 1943-1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Matthias, B., undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Matthias, B., undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Matthias, B., 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Matthias, B., 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bernd T. Matthias - Memoirs, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Student: O'Connor, Mike, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Murphy, D.W., undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Nellis, W.J., undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Pauling, Linus, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Pisharody, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Prober, D.E., undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Student: Robinson, Bennett, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Rogalla, Horst, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Student: Salem, Jesse, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Schawlow, A.L., undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Sleight, A.W., undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Snyder, Jeffrey G., undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Smith, T.F., undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Testardi, l., undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Van Dover, Bruce, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Solid State Physics, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)